Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Supplemental Files, 1952-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Supplemental Files
  - Searches 1983-2001
    - Vice President for Research, Office of the
      - 1998-1999 (Fawwaz Ulaby)
        - Finalist Files, 6 folders (Box 41)
    - Vice President for Student Affairs, Office of the
      - Vice President for Student Affairs
        - 1991 (Maureen Anderson Hartford)
          - Advertisement (Box 41)
          - Background on Student Affairs Office (Box 41)
          - Correspondence (Box 41)
          - Interviews (Box 41)
          - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 41)
          - Search Committee Membership (Box 41)
          - Finalist Files, 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Associate Vice President for Student Services
        - 1990 (Eunice Royster-Harper)
          - Advertisement (Box 41)
          - Candidates (Box 41)
          - Correspondence (Box 41)
          - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 41)
          - Royster-Harper, Eunice (Box 41)
    - Vice Provost for International Affairs and Director of the International Institute 1999 (Michael D. Kennedy)
    - Vice Provost for Minority [/Multicultural and Academic] Affairs
      - 1986-1987 (Charles Moody)
        - Background on Office of the Vice Provost for Minority Affairs (Box 41)
        - Charge to the Advisory Committee (Box 41)
        - Advisory Committee Final Report to the Provost (Box 41)
        - Advisory Committee Meetings (Box 41)
        - Advisory Committee Membership (Box 41)
        - Candidates (Box 41)
        - Finalists (Box 41)
        - Issues (Box 41)
        - Job Description (Box 41)
        - Publicity (Box 41)
        - Search Process (Box 41)
        - Moody, Charles (Box 41)
      - 1992-1993 (Lester Monts)
        - Advertisement (Box 41)
        - Background Information on the University of Michigan (Box 41)
        - Candidates (Box 41)
        - Correspondence (Box 41)
        - Evaluation of Candidates (Box 41)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 41)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 41)
        - Interview Questions (Box 41)
        - Letters Seeking Nominations (Box 41)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 41)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 41)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 41)
        - Search Consultants (Box 41)
        - Student Leader Lunches (Box 41)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Office of Minority Affairs Quality of Student Life Survey 1985
    The series Office of Minority Affairs Quality of Student Life Survey (1 lin. ft.) consists of a data code book and completed forms from a 1985 survey of student life. The survey was aimed at assessing the effectiveness of activities relating to the recruitment and retention of minority students. The survey was sent to a cross-section of students and measured academic as well as non-academic aspects of university life. Related documentation is available in the records of associate vice president Niara Sudarkasa in the Staff Files subgroup.
    - Data Book 1985 (Box 42)
    - Completed Survey Forms 1985 (Box 42)
  - Office Policy and Office Holder Documents 1982-1997
    - Office Policy Documents
      The Office Policy and Office Holder Documents series, 1982-1997 (1.4 lin. ft.), is comprised of reports and policies describing the operation and functions of the Provost's office and some biographical information on former vice presidents and provosts. Two volumes prepared in 1990 for the incoming office holder describe in detail the inner workings of the office and offer some historic insight into policy positions. Also included here are files on some of the vice presidents and provosts beginning with Billy E. Frye. Material includes copies of curricula vitae, clippings, and speeches and presentations made Frye, Charles M. Vest, Gilbert Whitaker, and Bernard Machen.
      - Provost Transition Documents July 1990, 2 volumes (Box 43)
      - Policies and Procedures 1983-1993 (Box 43)
    - Office Holders
      - Billy E. Frye
        - Biographical 1983-1986 (Box 43)
        - Farewell Function 1985 (Box 43)
        - Speeches and Presentations 1982-1986 (Box 43)
      - Charles M. Vest
        - Biographical (Box 43)
        - Speeches and Presentation 1989 (Box 43)
      - Gilbert R. Whitaker
        - Biographical 1990-1991 (Box 43)
        - Budget Presentations
          - General Fund July 16, 1992 (Box 43)
          - Sep. 17 1992 (Box 43)
          - State Budget Request, Oct 15 1992 (Box 43)
          - General Fund July 15, 1993 (Box 43)
          - September 24, 1993 (Box 43)
          - State Budget Request, Oct 22 1993 (Box 43)
          - January 20, 1994 (Box 43)
          - State Budget Request, Oct 20 1994 (Box 43)
          - Value Centered Management February 16, 1995 (Box 43)
          - April 20, 1995 (Box 43)
        - Budget Documents
          - FY 92-93 July 1992 (Box 43)
          - FY 93-94 July 1993 (Box 43)
          - FY 94-95 July 1994 (Box 43)
          - FY 95-96 July 1995 (Box 43)
          - FY 92-93 Tuition and Fees Document July 16, 1992 (Box 50)
          - FY 93-94 Tuition and Fees Document July 1993 (Box 50)
        - Other Presentations
          - Financial Aid Presentation to Regents (Box 50)
          - Rating Agency Presentation to Moody's Investors Service October 28, 1993 (Box 50)
          - Senate Higher Education Review, Feb 9 1994 (Box 50)
      - J. Bernard Machen 1995-1997
        - Biographical 1995 (Box 50)
        - Budget Presentations
          - Budget Presentation FY 96/97, July 18, 1996 (Box 50)
          - Budget Presentation FY 97/98, July 17, 1997 (Box 50)
          - State Budget Request FY 97 and FY 98 October 19, 1995 (Box 50)
          - State Budget Request FY 98 November 15, 1996 (Box 50)
          - VCM Presentation to Regents May 16, 1996 (Box 50)
        - Speeches
          - Commission for Women 25th Anniversary November 20, 1996 (Box 50)
          - Management Institute March 8, 1996 (Box 50)
          - Management Institute March 7, 1997 (Box 50)
          - Senate Assembly October 28, 1996 (Box 50)
          - Southern Illinois University at Edwardsville Commencement, Jun. 7 1997 (Box 50)
          - Women of Color December 6, 1995 (Box 50)
      - Robert S. Holbrook (Associate Provost)
        - Biographical (includes photo) ca. 1993-1997 (Box 50)
        - Fees and Financial Aid Presentation, Aug 6 1993 (Box 50)
        - Higher Education Task Force October 8, 1993 (Box 50)
        - Presentation to FWW Business & Finance Institute, Feb 5 1993 (Box 50)
        - State Budget Request FY 97 and FY 98, Working Documents October 19, 1995 (Box 50)
      - Robert B. Holmes (Assistant Vice President)
        - Biographical 1990 (Box 50)
  - Alliance for Undergraduate Education 1985-1995
    The Alliance for Undergraduate Education was formed in 1986 by a number of public research universities to develop and disseminate information about exemplary standards and practices in undergraduate education. Material in this series (1.0 lin. ft., 1985-1995) reflects those goals and includes information on the governance and administration of the Alliance as well as information on various programs in place at the University of Michigan and other universities in the Alliance. Michigan's representatives to the Alliance were Robert Holbrook, Mary Ann Swain, and Susan Lipschutz. In 1995 Michigan withdrew from the Alliance.
    - 1985-1995, 21 folders (Box 44)
  - Task Force on Campus Safety and Security 1992-1997
    The Task Force on Campus Safety and Security (TFCSS), 1992-1997 (1 lin. ft.), was appointed by the Provost on July 9, 1996, to review progress toward achieving the recommendations of the 1989 Task Force on Campus Safety and Security and to assess safety needs and perceptions on campus. The task force, chaired by Paul Boylan, began its work in the Fall of 1996 and submitted its report in April 1997. The task force was organized into five groups. Group I reviewed crime statistics at peer institutions and compared peer policies and operation with those at Michigan. Group II studied enhancements since 1990 including campus lighting and escort programs. Group III organized campus meetings with various constituencies to gauge community perceptions of safety and security. Group IV identified all campus agencies involved in conflict resolution with an emphasis on harassment. Group V focused on the Department of Public Safety, including policies, procedures, personnel, and budget. Documentation includes the charge to the task force, background material studied by the working groups, meeting minutes, as well as the final report. The final report contains extensive appendices, including a study by the Institute for Social Research (ISR) on "Perceptions of Safety and Security at the University of Michigan."
    - Final Report (includes drafts) 1997 (Box 45)
    - Appendixes, 2 volumes (Box 45)
    - Articles 1996-1997 (Box 45)
    - Common Characteristics of Letter and Parcel Bombs, ca. 1996 (Box 45)
    - General 1993-1997 (Box 45)
    - Members 1996-1997 (Box 45)
    - Meetings 1996-1997, 13 folders (Box 45)
    - Group I-Indexed Crime Review 1995-1997 (Box 45)
    - Group II-Environmental Safety (includes lighting studies) 1992-1997 (Box 45)
    - Group III-Perceptions of Safety 1997 (Box 45)
    - Group IV-University of Michigan Agencies Survey-Issues of Harassment and Conflict Resolution 1997 (Box 45)
    - Group V-Department of Public Safety Review (includes Special Event Guidelines) 1996-1997 (Box 45)
    - University Policies 1992-1996 (Box 45)
    - Women's Issues 1992-1996 (Box 45)
    - "Perceptions of Safety and Security at the University of Michigan" (ISR Survey and Study with Cross-Tables) 1997 (Box 45)
  - Child Care Task Force 1996-1998
    Records of the Child Care Task Force, 1996-1998 (0.5 lin. ft.), include the final report, background source material on related initiatives and policies both locally and nationally dating from 1991 to 1996, the charge to the task force, membership, and meeting minutes from 1996 to 1998.
    - Final Report 1998 (Box 46)
    - Source Book 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Membership, Charge, Minutes and Background 1996-1998 (Box 46)
  - Thurnau Trust and Thurnau Professorships 1979-2001
    The Thurnau Trust and Thurnau Professorships series, 1979-2001, (1 lin. ft.) includes the records of the administration of the bequest of Arthur F. Thurnau. Thurnau was student at the University between 1902 and 1904, and made the University the beneficiary of a bequest of approximately $3,000,000. The provost, Billy Frye, requested the faculty to submit proposals suggesting how the money should be employed, and in particular solicited ideas for research of intellectual significance and future promise. Several faculty members independently submitted proposals within the molecular genetics field, and Frye encouraged them to confer together and submit a joint, interdisciplinary proposal, which was funded through the proceeds of the trust.
    In 1988, the then provost, Jim Duderstadt, asked the Regents to repurpose the income from the Thurnau bequest to recognize and reward faculty for outstanding contributions to undergraduate education. The program honored tenured faculty whose commitment and investment in undergraduate teaching had a demonstrable impact on the intellectual development of Michigan students.
    - Proposals 1979-1981 (Box 46)
    - Molecular Genetics 1981-1986 (Box 46)
    - Arthur F. Thurnau Professorships 1988-2001, 14 folders (Box 47)
      [PR RESTRICTED until 2031 ]
  - Career Development Fund for Women Faculty 1994-1999
    The records of the Career Development Fund for Women Faculty, 1994-1999, (2.7 lin. ft.) illustrate the efforts of the provost to ease the administrative burden placed on women faculty members. Because of their small numbers, women often carried a disproportionate commitment for student advising, department, college and University committees, dissertation committees, and other service activities. This program awarded $5,000 each to female tenured and tenure-track faculty members who demonstrated professional achievement and significant service (other than classroom teaching). The award was to be used to support graduate students, travel or research materials. The records typically contain the applicant's vita, a statement about her service commitments, and an evaluator's form. It is a very good source for an interdisciplinary sampling of women faculty CV's for this period.
    - Fall 1994
      - Awardees
        - Adams, Julia (Box 47)
        - Anspach, Renee (Box 47)
        - Bell, Betty Louise (Box 47)
        - Burbank, Jane (Box 47)
        - Fries, Marilyn (Box 47)
        - Graham-Berman, Sandra (Box 47)
        - Howard, June (Box 47)
        - Karlsen, Carol (Box 47)
        - Kieffer, Edith (Box 47)
        - Krisch, Jean (Box 47)
        - Levenstein, Margaret (Box 47)
        - Low, Bobbi (Box 47)
        - Lubeck, Sally (Box 47)
        - Orbuch, Terri (Box 47)
        - Peyser, Patricia (Box 47)
        - Punch, Margaret (Box 47)
        - Robertson, Jennifer (Box 47)
        - Rock, Cheryl (Box 47)
        - Rose, Sonya (Box 47)
        - Zirbes, Georgette (Box 47)
      - Nominees
        - Alcock, Susan (Box 47)
        - Anderson, Barbara (Box 47)
        - Anderson-Levitt, Kathryn (Box 47)
        - Ashford, Susan (Box 47)
        - Baggett, Patricia Barald, Kate (Box 47)
        - Barnard, Ruth (Box 47)
        - Bartlett, Rosamund (Box 47)
        - Becker, Jill (Box 47)
        - Behar, Ruth (Box 47)
        - Bike, Stacy (Box 47)
        - Bozynski, Mary (Box 47)
        - Bradford, Carol (Box 47)
        - Brooks, Christine (Box 47)
        - Brooks, Sharon (Box 47)
        - Burnham, Robyn (Box 47)
        - Camper, Sally (Box 47)
        - Canning, Kathleen (Box 47)
        - Carroll, Mary Anne (Box 47)
        - Cheng, Migonette Yin (Box 47)
        - Connell, Cathleen (Box 47)
        - Cooney, Kathleen (Box 47)
        - Delanghe, Gay Ann (Box 47)
        - Dewar, Margaret (Box 47)
        - Downs, Laura (Box 47)
        - Faller, Kathleen (Box 47)
        - Feldman, Eva (Box 47)
        - Florida, Nancy (Box 47)
        - Gibson, Rose (Box 47)
        - Gilsdorf, Janet (Box 47)
        - Gocek, Fatma Muge (Box 47)
        - Goldberg, Deborah (Box 47)
        - Gregerson, Linda (Box 47)
        - Gross, M. Melissa (Box 47)
        - Gunning, Sandra (Box 47)
        - Guthrie, Sally (Box 47)
        - Hardwick, Janis (Box 47)
        - Harrington, Helen (Box 47)
        - Haslanger, Sally (Box 47)
        - Hoffman, Lois (Box 47)
        - Israel, Barbara (Box 47)
        - Johnson, Marilyn (Box 47)
        - Kaplan, Rachel (Box 47)
        - Kazerooni, Ella (Box 47)
        - Kearfott, Kim (Box 47)
        - Keller Cohen, Deborah (Box 47)
        - Kent, Claudia (Box 47)
        - Kohut, Karen (Box 47)
        - Krook, Ann (Box 47)
        - Lippi-Green, Rosina (Box 47)
        - MacCormick, Sabine (Box 47)
        - Martel, Mary Kaye (Box 47)
        - Mistretta, Charlotte (Box 47)
        - Montgomery, Susan (Box 48)
        - Moss, Thylias (Box 48)
        - Nasr, Samya (Box 48)
        - Nichols, Ruthann (Box 48)
        - Olson, Sheryl (Box 48)
        - Palincsar, Annemarie (Box 48)
        - Pang, Stella (Box 48)
        - Reame, Nancy (Box 48)
        - Reed, Beth Glover (Box 48)
        - Robins, Diane (Box 48)
        - Roubidoux, Marilyn (Box 48)
        - Russell, Melinda (Box 48)
        - Samuelson, Linda (Box 48)
        - Saxonhouse, Arlene (Box 48)
        - Scodel, Ruth (Box 48)
        - Seifert, Colleen (Box 48)
        - Shadigian, Elizabeth (Box 48)
        - Silver, Dorit (Box 48)
        - Simmons, Mila (Box 48)
        - Simms, Lillian (Box 48)
        - Simpson, Patricia (Box 48)
        - Sowers, MaryFran (Box 48)
        - Stecke, Kathryn (Box 48)
        - Sutton, Sharon (Box 48)
        - Terada, Rei (Box 48)
        - Therrien, Barbara (Box 48)
        - Thompson, Deborah (Box 48)
        - Tinkle, Theresa (Box 48)
        - Van Dyke, Rebecca (Box 48)
        - Weiss, Sharon (Box 48)
        - Zafar, Rafia (Box 48)
    - Spring 1995
      - Awardees
        - Adams, Barbara (Box 48)
        - Brake, Mary (Box 48)
        - Brown, Elsa (Box 48)
        - Buyse, Leone (Box 48)
        - Canning, Kathleen (Box 48)
        - Downs, Laura (Box 48)
        - Ellison, Julie (Box 48)
        - Erickson, Donna (Box 48)
        - Groat, Linda (Box 48)
        - Haslanger, Sally (Box 48)
        - Herbert, Sharon (Box 48)
        - Kearfott, Kimberlee (Box 48)
        - King, Miriam (Box 48)
        - Lippi-Green, Rosina (Box 48)
        - McCauley, Laurie (Box 48)
        - Palincsar, Annemarie (Box 48)
        - Shively, JoEllen (Box 48)
        - Simons, Pat (Box 48)
        - Smith, Joanne (Box 48)
        - Volling, Brenda (Box 48)
      - Nominees
        - Alcock, Susan (Box 48)
        - Aparicio, Frances (Box 48)
        - Arruda, Ellen (Box 48)
        - Ball, Arnetha (Box 48)
        - Biermann, J. Sybil (Box 48)
        - Brown, Elsa Barkley (Box 48)
        - Burnham, Robyn (Box 48)
        - Camper, Sally (Box 48)
        - Carpenter, Bogdana (Box 48)
        - Carroll, Mary Anne (Box 48)
        - Clej, Alina (Box 48)
        - Cooney, Kathleen (Box 48)
        - Feldman, Eva (Box 48)
        - Feldman, Martha (Box 48)
        - Finkel, Elizabeth (Box 48)
        - Freese, Katherine (Box 48)
        - Gazda, Elaine (Box 48)
        - Gere, Anne (Box 48)
        - Gocek, Fatma (Box 48)
        - Goldberg, Deborah (Box 48)
        - Gregg, Veronica (Box 48)
        - Gross, Melissa (Box 48)
        - Gunning, Sandra Rose (Box 48)
        - Guthrie, Barbara (Box 48)
        - Harrington, Helen (Box 48)
        - Hart, Janet (Box 48)
        - Highfill, Juli (Box 48)
        - Hoffman, Lois (Box 48)
        - Israel, Kali (Box 48)
        - Krook, Anne (Box 48)
        - Lange, Rebecca (Box 48)
        - Leonard, Joanne (Box 48)
        - Masson, Annette (Box 48)
        - McPhail, Jean (Box 48)
        - Mistretta, Charlotte (Box 48)
        - Montgomery, Susan (Box 48)
        - Norich, Anita (Box 48)
        - Olsen, Laura (Box 48)
        - Pang, Stella (Box 48)
        - Petruzzelli, Lilli (Box 48)
        - Robins, Diane (Box 48)
        - Root, Terry (Box 48)
        - Rundensteiner, Elke (Box 48)
        - Samuelson, Linda (Box 48)
        - Saxonhouse, Arlene (Box 48)
        - Schipani, Cindy (Box 48)
        - Simpson, Patricia (Box 48)
        - Skantze, P.A. (Box 48)
        - Somers, Margaret (Box 48)
        - Stecke, Kathryn (Box 48)
        - Sun, Jiayang (Box 48)
        - Thompson, Debra (Box 48)
        - Tucker, Priscilla (Box 48)
    - Fall 1995
      - Awardees
        - Anderson, Shannon (Box 48)
        - Arruda, Ellen (Box 48)
        - Bartlett, Rosamund (Box 48)
        - Boyd, Carol (Box 48)
        - Bradford, Carol (Box 48)
        - Briggs, Josie (Box 48)
        - Burnham, Robyn (Box 48)
        - Camper, Sally (Box 48)
        - Carroll, Mary Anne (Box 48)
        - Clej, Alina (Box 48)
        - Crow, Heidi (Box 48)
        - Dewar, Margaret (Box 48)
        - Drabenstott, Karen (Box 48)
        - Feldman, Martha (Box 48)
        - Gazda, Elaine (Box 48)
        - Goldberg, Deborah (Box 48)
        - Gross, M. Melissa (Box 48)
        - Hart, Janet (Box 48)
        - Kazerooni, Ella (Box 48)
        - Lee, Theresa (Box 48)
        - Leonard, Joanne (Box 48)
        - Lin, Xihong (Box 48)
        - Loch-Caruso, Rita (Box 48)
        - McLaughlin, Catherine (Box 48)
        - Merajver, Sofia (Box 48)
        - Norich, Anita (Box 48)
        - Pang, Stella (Box 48)
        - Pedraza, Silvia (Box 48)
        - Pohl, Joanne (Box 48)
        - Rathcke, Beverly (Box 48)
        - Rodriguez-Hornedo, Nair (Box 48)
        - Root, Margaret (Box 48)
        - Rundersteiner, Elke (Box 48)
        - Scodel, Ruth (Box 48)
        - Seifert, Colleen (Box 48)
        - Somers, Margaret (Box 48)
        - Stein, Louise (Box 48)
        - Thompson, Debra (Box 48)
        - Yeo, SeonAe (Box 48)
      - Nominees
        - Barald, Kate (Box 48)
        - Becker, Judith (Box 48)
        - Coleman-Burns, Patricia (Box 48)
        - Cooney, Kathleen (Box 48)
        - Feldman, Eva (Box 48)
        - Finkel, Elizabeth (Box 48)
        - Fuller, Oveta (Box 48)
        - Gere, Anne Ruggles (Box 48)
        - Gocek, Fatma Muge (Box 48)
        - Haefner, Hope Katharine (Box 48)
        - Harlow, Sioban (Box 48)
        - Israel, Barbara (Box 48)
        - Johnson, Marilyn (Box 48)
        - Kaplan, Rachel (Box 48)
        - Kauffman, Carol (Box 48)
        - Lange, Rebecca (Box 48)
        - Lee, Valerie (Box 48)
        - Malow, Beth (Box 48)
        - Montgomery, Susan (Box 48)
        - O'Shea, K. Sue (Box 48)
        - Perfecto, Ivette (Box 48)
        - Robins, Diane (Box 48)
        - Robinson, Sally (Box 48)
        - Root, Terry (Box 48)
        - Samuelson, Linda (Box 48)
        - Saxenhouse, Arlene (Box 48)
        - Shewach, Donna (Box 48)
        - Simmons, Milagros (Box 48)
        - Stecke, Kathryn (Box 48)
        - Sutton, Sharon (Box 48)
        - Telesnitsky, Alice (Box 48)
        - White, Michelle (Box 48)
    - 1996
      - Awardees
        - Alcock, Susan E. (Box 49)
        - Barald, Kate F. (Box 49)
        - Becker, Jill B. (Box 49)
        - Beddor, Patrice Speeter (Box 49)
        - Brusati, Celeste (Box 49)
        - Cameron, Judith Wynn (Box 49)
        - Feldman, Eva L. (Box 49)
        - Foxman, Betsy (Box 49)
        - Frost, C. Olivia (Box 49)
        - Gaither, Caroline A. (Box 49)
        - Gregerson, Linda (Box 49)
        - Haefner, Hope Katharine (Box 49)
        - Harlow, Sioban D. (Box 49)
        - Herrmann, Anne (Box 49)
        - Hogan, Mary M. (Box 49)
        - Hurtado, Sylvia (Box 49)
        - Jenkins, Janice M. (Box 49)
        - Juster, Susan (Box 49)
        - Keller-Cohen, Deborah (Box 49)
        - Maddock, Janine (Box 49)
        - Marx, M. Victoria (Box 49)
        - Olsen, Laura J. (Box 49)
        - Omann, Geneva M. (Box 49)
        - Petty, Elizabeth M. (Box 49)
        - Robins, Diane M. (Box 49)
        - Sastry, Ann Marie (Box 49)
        - Shadigian, Elizabeth (Box 49)
        - Siefert, Kristine (Box 49)
        - Smith, Sherri (Box 49)
        - Stark, Joan S. (Box 49)
        - Stecke, Kathryn E. (Box 49)
        - Sutton, Sharon E. (Box 49)
        - van Hoek, Karen (Box 49)
        - Walker, Deborah S. (Box 49)
        - Wang, Caroline (Box 49)
        - Yaeger, Patricia (Box 49)
    - 1998
      - Awardees
        - Andre, Naomi (Box 49)
        - Caulfied, Sueann (Box 49)
        - Dunkle, Ruth E. (Box 49)
        - Florida, Nancy K. (Box 49)
        - Fredrickson, Barbara L. (Box 49)
        - Gnegy, Margaret E. (Box 49)
        - Gutierrez, Lorraine M. (Box 49)
        - Lin, Ann Chih (Box 49)
        - Martin, Karin A. (Box 49)
        - Montoya, Maria E. (Box 49)
        - Murray, Susan (Box 49)
        - Porter, Marianetta (Box 49)
        - Raisler, Jeanne (Box 49)
        - Rowe, Ellen H. (Box 49)
        - Stephens, Sharon (Box 49)
        - Stewart, Abigail (Box 49)
        - Swanson, Michele S. (Box 49)
        - Takata, Azumi Ann (Box 49)
        - Tonomura, Hitomi (Box 49)
        - Wingrove, Elizabeth (Box 49)
        - Yoshihama, Mieko (Box 49)
      - Nominees
        - Biermann, J. Sybil (Box 49)
        - Cooney, Kathleen (Box 49)
        - Foster, Carol (Box 49)
        - Gelman, Susan (Box 49)
        - Ghaziuddin, Neera (Box 49)
        - Goldman, Rachel (Box 49)
        - Goold, Susan (Box 49)
        - Johnson, Marilyn (Box 49)